Nongyu.
نونجيو.
I found Mom.
لقد وجدت أمي.
Mom, I want to tell you something.
أمي، أريد أن أخبرك بشيء.
Last week, a new classmate
في الأسبوع الماضي، زميل جديد في الصف
saw the scarf you knitted for me and said it was beautiful.
رأيت الوشاح الذي حيكته لي وقلت إنه جميل.
Does that make you happy?
هل هذا يجعلك سعيداً؟
The last time I saw you,
آخر مرة رأيتك فيها،
your forehead was like burning.
كانت جبهتك تحترق.
This time, it is not like that at all.
هذه المرة، الأمر ليس كذلك على الإطلاق.
That means my blood
هذا يعني دمي
really helps with your illness.
يساعد ذلك حقاً في علاج مرضك.
Right?
يمين؟
Is your dad using your blood to treat your mom?
هل يستخدم والدك دمك لعلاج والدتك؟
Mom got very, very sick.
مرضت أمي بشدة.
She slept for a very long time.
نامت لفترة طويلة جداً.
Dad tried every way he could.
حاول أبي بكل الطرق الممكنة.
In the end, he realized...
وفي النهاية، أدرك...
I was the one who could save her.
كنت أنا من يستطيع إنقاذها.
But what if
لكن ماذا لو
your mom does not get better,
لن تتحسن والدتك،
and it ends up hurting you?
وينتهي الأمر بإيذائك؟
Big guy,
رجل ضخم،
you and my brother
أنت وأخي
are saying the same dumb thing.
يقولون نفس الكلام الغبي.
Look.
ينظر.
Mom has always smelt nice.
لطالما كانت رائحة أمي جميلة.
When I go to classmates' homes to do homework,
عندما أذهب إلى منازل زملائي في الفصل لأداء واجباتي المدرسية،
their sick family members smell bad.
أفراد عائلاتهم المرضى تنبعث منهم رائحة كريهة.
That means Mom is getting better every day.
هذا يعني أن أمي تتحسن يوماً بعد يوم.
♪The wind is calm tonight♪
♪الريح هادئة الليلة♪
♪Looking for answers in the dark♪
♪ نبحث عن إجابات في الظلام ♪
Thank you, big guy.
شكراً لك يا رجل.
Dad never wants to bring me here.
أبي لا يريد أبداً أن يأتي بي إلى هنا.
You helped me fulfill
لقد ساعدتني في تحقيق هدفي
my wish of seeing Mom.
أمنيتي هي رؤية أمي.
I'm really, really happy.
أنا سعيد للغاية.
I won't be afraid of blood draws anymore.
لن أخاف من سحب الدم بعد الآن.
At least,
على الأقل،
not for a whole month.
ليس لمدة شهر كامل.
You still have to go back?
هل ما زلت مضطراً للعودة؟
Of course I have to go home after seeing Mom.
بالطبع يجب أن أعود إلى المنزل بعد رؤية أمي.
Otherwise, Dad will cry.
وإلا، سيبكي أبي.
You don't know, every time after they draw my blood,
أنت لا تعلم، في كل مرة بعد أن يسحبوا دمي،
and after Dad coaxes me to sleep,
وبعد أن يُقنعني أبي بالنوم،
he secretly cries in his room for a long time.
يبكي سراً في غرفته لفترة طويلة.
He is really pitiful.
إنه مثير للشفقة حقاً.
♪Living for dreams...♪
♪أعيش من أجل الأحلام...♪
Nongyu!
نونجيو!
Give my daughter back to me.
أعيدوا لي ابنتي.
Go.
يذهب.
I'll take you somewhere safe.
سآخذك إلى مكان آمن.
Big guy,
رجل ضخم،
you really do not get what is going on.
أنت حقاً لا تفهم ما يجري.
You are the one who needs protection.
أنت من يحتاج إلى الحماية.
Dad must have mistaken you for a bad guy.
لا بد أن أبي قد ظنك شخصاً سيئاً.
There is no way to explain it right now.
لا توجد طريقة لشرح ذلك الآن.
Hurry and climb out through the window.
أسرع واصعد للخارج من النافذة.
♪Hold that your fragile paper heart♪
♪امسك بقلبك الورقي الهش♪
♪Hope for the first time♪
♪أمل لأول مرة♪
♪It would start to heal all on its own♪
♪سيبدأ بالشفاء من تلقاء نفسه♪
♪Like wavering candles in the rain♪
♪كشموع متذبذبة تحت المطر♪
♪You so surprised to see the flames has gone out once more♪
♪هل أنت مندهشٌ للغاية لرؤية أن النيران قد انطفأت مرة أخرى؟♪
Was it all a dream?
هل كان كل ذلك مجرد حلم؟
Such a handsome big guy.
رجل ضخم وسيم للغاية.
I wonder if I will ever see him again.
أتساءل إن كنت سأراه مرة أخرى.
Big guy, you have not left yet?
يا رجل ضخم، ألم تغادر بعد؟
It was sleep-talking.
كان يتحدث أثناء نومه.
I did not dream about you.
لم أحلم بك.
Really?
حقًا؟
But I did dream about you,
لكنني حلمت بك،
and you were in fifth grade.
وكنتَ في الصف الخامس.
And your parents.
ووالديك.
So you too...
وأنت أيضاً...
I also dreamed about you.
لقد حلمت بك أيضاً.
I even dreamed
حتى أنني حلمت
that I went to your university
أنني التحقت بجامعتكم
and your home.
ومنزلك.
I met your parents too.
قابلت والديك أيضاً.
It feels like we stepped into each other's dreams.
يبدو الأمر وكأننا دخلنا أحلام بعضنا البعض.
But there is no time to think about that now.
لكن ليس هناك وقت للتفكير في ذلك الآن.
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
Max could catch up to us at any moment.
قد يلحق بنا ماكس في أي لحظة.
We need to find the fragments fast.
نحتاج إلى العثور على الشظايا بسرعة.
We are out of gas.
لقد نفد منا الوقود.
We will have to go on foot.
سيتعين علينا السير على الأقدام.
Can you keep going?
هل يمكنك الاستمرار؟
You okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
There's something over there.
هناك شيء ما هناك.
Careful.
انتبه.
This just looks like an ordinary piece of glass.
هذا يبدو مجرد قطعة زجاج عادية.
That's so creative.
هذا إبداعٌ للغاية.
Storing information like this.
تخزين معلومات كهذه.
In this world,
في هذا العالم،
there are even more amazing things.
وهناك أشياء أكثر إثارة للدهشة.
For example...
على سبيل المثال...
Do you believe
هل تعتقد
that there are dragons still alive?
هل ما زالت التنانين موجودة؟
You are not saying
أنت لا تقول
you brought a dragon back to life from fossils, are you?
هل قمت بإعادة تنين إلى الحياة من الأحافير؟
Do you really need to laugh that hard?
هل أنت حقاً بحاجة إلى الضحك بهذا القدر؟
This is more than just a scratch.
هذا أكثر من مجرد خدش.
You are seriously stubborn.
أنت عنيد للغاية.
Get up.
استيقظ.
Stay down with me a little longer.
ابقَ معي لفترة أطول قليلاً.
Five minutes will do.
خمس دقائق تكفي.
Then, we will cross the mountain ahead.
ثم سنعبر الجبل أمامنا.
If we go back the same way,
إذا عدنا من نفس الطريق،
we'll easily run into Max and the others.
سنلتقي بسهولة بماكس والآخرين.
But how are you supposed to climb a mountain
لكن كيف يُفترض بك أن تتسلق جبلاً؟
in your condition?
في حالتك؟
There is actually a way for me to get my strength back,
هناك بالفعل طريقة لاستعادة قوتي،
but I need your help.
لكنني أحتاج مساعدتك.
Comfort me
هَدِّئني
as you did in my dream.
كما فعلتَ في حلمي.
You mean
تقصد
when the viral load spikes,
عندما يرتفع الحمل الفيروسي بشكل حاد،
my virus
فيروسي
can inhibit yours,
قد يعيق ذلك قدرتك،
and when your load drops too low,
وعندما ينخفض ​​حمولتك إلى مستوى منخفض للغاية،
I can also
يمكنني أيضًا
trigger yours?
هل ستثير هذه المشاعر مشاعرك؟
That sounds way too absurd.
هذا يبدو سخيفاً للغاية.
I am messing with you.
أنا أمزح معك.
♪City lights, hazy lines♪
أضواء المدينة، خطوط ضبابية
♪Running into a peculiar kind of crime♪
♪مواجهة نوع غريب من الجرائم♪
♪Accomplices in passion♪
♪ شركاء في العاطفة ♪
♪Shared a sweet damnation♪
♪شاركنا لعنة حلوة♪
♪Shedding the skin, the consequence♪
♪ التخلص من الجلد، والنتيجة ♪
♪Heaven's gates open wide for a time♪
♪تُفتح أبواب السماء على مصراعيها لبعض الوقت♪
♪Once you cross the line of flame♪
♪بمجرد أن تتجاوز خط اللهب♪
How is it now?
كيف حالها الآن؟
My legs are turning weak from your kisses.
أشعر بضعف في ساقيّ من كثرة قبلاتك.
Then, let's move out.
ثم، فلننتقل.
Xie Xinxu.
شيه شينكسو.
Your kiss
قبلتك
really does work.
إنه فعال حقاً.
Why do you feel heavier and heavier?
لماذا تشعر بثقل متزايد؟
You can't just stop trying
لا يمكنك ببساطة التوقف عن المحاولة
and dump all your weight on me.
وألقِ بكل ثقلك عليّ.
Use some strength yourself.
استخدم بعض قوتك بنفسك.
Xie Xinxu.
شيه شينكسو.
Xie Xinxu, you can't fall asleep.
شي شينشو، لا يمكنك النوم.
Boss,
رئيس،
there is blood here.
هناك دماء هنا.
Go after them!
انطلقوا وراءهم!
Xie Xinxu.
شيه شينكسو.
Get up.
استيقظ.
Move.
يتحرك.
Xie Xinxu.
شيه شينكسو.
Get up.
استيقظ.
Don't fall asleep!
لا تغفو!
Xie Xinxu.
شيه شينكسو.
Get up.
استيقظ.
Who told you to fire?
من سمح لك بالطرد؟
I...
أنا...
I just saw the grass moving over there.
رأيت العشب يتحرك هناك.
I thought...
ظننت...
If your eyes fail you again...
إذا خانتك عيناك مرة أخرى...
we'll make him a display piece.
سنجعله قطعة عرض.
What do you say?
ما رأيك؟
Boss, they went that way.
يا رئيس، لقد ذهبوا من ذلك الطريق.
They didn't head uphill.
لم يتجهوا صعوداً.
Chase them!
طاردهم!
You've got quite a few tricks.
لديك الكثير من الحيل.
But you smell too strong.
لكن رائحتك قوية جداً.
Where is my Xu?
أين شو خاصتي؟
He's hiding somewhere, of course,
هو مختبئ في مكان ما، بالطبع.
waiting to catch you off guard.
في انتظار أن يفاجئك.
Xu,
شو،
are you not coming out?
ألن تخرج؟
come out and say goodbye.
اخرج وقل وداعاً.
Fine.
بخير.
For couples like you,
للأزواج مثلك،
a "Bad End" makes for a better story.
النهاية السيئة تجعل القصة أفضل.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪